Siddhartha Chakraborti

13 YEARS EXPERIENCE IN SKILL IMPLEMENTATION , OPERATIONS AS WELL AS MONITORING.

Kolkata, West Bengal siddharthachakraborti5_57f@indeedemail.com 9038383189

Flexible and participative member with 13+ years of operation, parts, delivery and quality and operations management experience directing the efforts of up to 100+ personnel to maintain and safeguard the process of project management. Strategic planner who optimizes manpower and budgetary funds that meet project needs and deliver high quality services. Balance meticulous attention to quality and detail with a sense of urgency to get the job done on-time and meet goals in fast-paced environments. Dedicated to creating a collaborative team environment where each member can develop and play an active role towards a fruitful result.

#readytowork

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

State Head QUALITY

RSWM Limited - Patna, Bihar January 2020 to Present

Working as project state head, Quality since January 2020.

Regional Manager

Orion Edutech - Kolkata, West Bengal April 2017 to December 2019

looking

after DDU-GKY Jharkhand since 2017 for the current organization.

9. Human Resource - Have done recruitment for various corporate and Govt projects in different states.

Senior Executive - Operations

Shriram New Horizons Ltd - Noida, Uttar Pradesh September 2007 to March 2017

Job Profile / Work Experience:

- 1. Training and Skill Development: Worked Technical Trainer and consultant for corporate and in Govt projects.
- 2. Logistics and Movement: Logistics operations like movement of materials in different locations and projects through land and cargo for all the states of India. Tying up with travel agencies for ticket booking and delivery, payments as well as executing agreements as per best option available. Application of pass /identity cards / professional tax related processing, time or role scheduling, procurement of office materials.

- 3. Recruitment Payroll Management and Attendance: As per of operations team and State/Project coordinator I have experience in recruitment, salary negotiation, induction as well as attendance maintenance. Recruited hundreds of temporary and permanent stuff in all over India as well as North East.
- 4. Project Management: Communication with authorities regarding different ongoing projects, documentation, and movement of skilled persons and submission of documents as per requirement of the project. Posted several years months in Shillong/Aizawl/Itanagar/Guwahati/Imphal for different Govt. Project. Taken care of recruitment, Business Associate Payment & day to day activities of both the facilities.
- 5. Client Management: Regular meetings with Govt. and corporate clients to schedule different projects Taking care of different deliveries in different locations of East and North East India on behalf of NICSI, Delhi for the Ministry of Panchayati Raj and Rural Development, Ministry of HRD, Ministry of personnel, public grievance & pensions and many more.
- 6. Operations: Traveled extensively in all Eastern and North Eastern States for Project Execution and Operations. Participated in tendering process as well.
- 7. Administration (Tech/Nontech): Have the responsibility of Technical Admin of Kolkata Office and two client sites at Kolkata. In charge of remote administration and operational issues of remote sites of Tripura, Meghalaya, Andaman Nicobar and Assam Office.

Support Admin for the clients like "Hero Honda"

Minisoft Solutions Kolkata - Kolkata, West Bengal January 2006 to December 2006

Jan 2006 - Dec 2006)-It is a Kolkata based company giving technical training/Software support to Automobile companies. Worked as Support Admin for the clients like "Hero Honda".

Education

Master's in ADMIN & HR 2ND SEMESTER

ISBM - Kolkata, West Bengal Present

GRADUATION in English

Calcutta University - Kolkata, West Bengal 2004

Skills / IT Skills

18 MONTHS CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER HARDWARE AND NETWORKING (10+ years)

Certifications and Licenses

VERBAL ENGLISH FROM BRITISH INSTITUTE

April 2004 to Present

Additional Information

Diploma in Hardware Networking from George Telegraph, Kolkata. Certified in RHCE / Completed CCNA Course on Verbal English from BBC. SOP Certificate: DATE: July 2, 2019 MC 02009014149